Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Albany Steel Co. vs. Local 469, IBT, 8/70. #70-536, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Transfer, Fighting
- Union Camp Corp. vs. Local 2, IBPSPMW, 5/12/70. #70-537, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Union Representative, Strike
- New York City Board of Education vs. UFT- Re: Myron Lowery, 5/1/70. #70-538, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- National Shoes vs. District 65, RWDSU, 5/18/70. #70-539, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Crew Size, Layoff
- Signal Delivery Service vs. Local 814, IBT, 4/20/70. #70-540, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Contract, Correspondence - Reporting Pay
- Ossining Board of Education vs. Ossining Teachers Association, 4/70. #70-541, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Mediator's Notes, Newspaper Article, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- A.P. Smith Valve Div. of U.S. Pipe & Foundry Co. Local 2013, USW, 4/30/70. #70-542, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee's Opening Statement, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Timeliness, Holiday Pay
- Schlang Woolen Co. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/5/70. #70-543, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Timeliness, Insubordination
- Allied New York Service, Inc. vs. Local 553, IBT, 3/30/70. #70-543, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Improper Personal Conduct, Insubordination
- Trust Company of New Jersey vs. Local 3142, OPEU, 5/70. #70-545, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Memorandum, Employee Memorandum, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Severance Pay
- Reynolds Metal Co. vs. Local 450, AWIU, 9/30/70. #70-546, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Decision, Hearing Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Briefs, Employee Briefs, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Schedules of Work, Holidays, Overtime
- Eastchester Board of Education vs. Eastchester Teachers Assn., 4/70. #70-547, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Mediator's Notes, Contract Proposals, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- E.R. Squibb & Sons, Inc. vs. Local 8-438, OCAWIU, 5/18/70. #70-548, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Memorandum, Joint Exhibit, Contract, Correspondence - Fights, Discharge
- Atlas Chrysler Plymouth vs. Local 259, UAW, 5/70. #70-549, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Valhalla Board of Education vs. Valhalla Teachers Assn., 6/19/70. #70-550 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendation, Fact-Finders Notes, PERB Rules & Appointment of Fact-Finder, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Contract, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Blue Comet Express vs. Local 641, IBT, 5/19/70. #70-551 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Incompetence & Improper Work
- Standard Brands, Inc. vs. Local 142, OPEIU, 5/70, #70-552, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Correspondence - Bargaining Unit Work by Supervisors
- Simmonds Precision, Inc. vs. Local 452, IUE, 4/15/70, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  Correspondence - Mutually Settled by the Parties
- City of New York vs. Local 1359, AFSCME, 8/4/70. #70-554, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendation, Fact-Finders Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Salary
- Yorktown Central School Dist. No. 2 vs. Yorktown Faculty Assn., 5/27/70. #70-555., 1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Report of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, PERB Instructions, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Mahopac School Dist. No. 1 vs. The Mahopac Teachers Assn. 6/17/70. #70-556, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employer Notes, Employee Contract Proposals, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Builders Institute of Westchester & Putnam Counties, Inc. vs. Building Trade Employers Association of Westchester & Putnam Counties and General Building Laborers District Council of Westchester County, NY, Laborers' International Union of North Am, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Overtime Pay
- Broadway Express, Inc. vs. Local 701, IBT, 6/1/70. #70-558, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Theft, Quits
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. United Federation of Teachers, 11/2/70. #70-559, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation, Past Practices
- Powell-Savory Corp. vs. newspaper Guild of NY, 6/70. #70-560, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Memorandum, Correspondence - Fringe Benefits
- Children's Village vs. Frank Fornario, 6/29/70. #70-561., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Strike, Sick Leave, Burden of Proof
- Star Industries, Inc. vs. Local 1, WLDWU, 8/20/70. #70-563, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employee Brief, Employer Post Hearing Brief, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Theft
- Bayview Nursing Center vs. Local 1115, NHU, 7/70. #70-564., 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Correspondence - Contract Negotiations (Mutually Settled by Parties)
- Alloy Flange & Fitting Corp. vs. Local 966, IBT, 6/2/70. #70-565, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Yellow Freight System vs. Local 641, Merchandise Drivers, 5/70. #70-566, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Somers Central School District, No. 1 vs. Somers Faculty Association, 9/16/70.#70-567, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Report of Fact & Recommendations, PERB Procedural Notes, Fact Finder's Notes, Employer's Contract Proposals, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Julius Schmid, Inc. vs. Local 404, UERMW, 8/6/70, #70-568, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Absences, Leaves of Absence
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. Warren Christenson, 1/22/71. #70-569, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Vacancies
- Borough of Ringwood vs. Local 1960, AFSCME, 6/17/70. #70-570, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Wages, Contract Interpretation
- Clifton Board of Education vs. Clifton Teachers Association, 7/7/70. #70-571, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation, Medical Insurance
- Wyckoff Heights Hospital vs. Local 144, SEIU, 8/17/70. #70-572, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Contract, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation
- Port Chester UFSD No. 4, Board of Education vs. Port Chester Teacher's Association, 8/70. #70-573, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  Report of Fact & Recommendation, Fact-Finder's Notes, PERB Memorandum, Employee Proposals, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Contract, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Allied New York Services, Inc. vs. Local 553, IBT, 7/17/70. #70-574, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Past Arbitration Awards, Correspondence - Safety, Negligence & Carelessness
- Cherry Valley Dairy, Inc. vs. Local 584, IBT, 6/15/70. #70-575, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. Local 102, IBT, 1/11/71, #70-576, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Decision. Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Vacations
- Westvaco Corp. H & D Container Div. Hoboken, NJ vs. Local 300, IBPSPMW, 9/21/70. #70-577, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Overtime, Temporary Transfers
- Board of Education, Levittown vs. David Armstrong, 7/17/70. #70-578, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Termination of Employment, Notice
- R.R. Squibb & Sons vs. Local 8-438, OCAWIU, 6/19/70. #70-579 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Famous Envelope Co. Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 7/10/70. #70-580, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Dishonesty
- CBS Records, A Div. of Colombia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 1/18/71. #70-581, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  Decision, Issue, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, General Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Jurisdiction
- Yale & Towne, Inc. vs. Local 78, Boilmakers, 8/70. #70-582, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- City Planning Commission vs. District Council 37, 10/23/70. #70-583, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Information to Arbitrator, hearing Transcript, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation, Conflict Over Opinion of Law, Probationary Period
- Ossining Board of Education vs. Ossining Teacher's Association, 7/70. #70-584, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Correspondence -
- T & N Restaurant Corp. vs. Local 1115, RDRLEU, 11/2/70. #70-586, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Credibility, Absenteeism, Quits
- Merganthaler Linotype Co. vs. Local 365, UAW, 10/21/70. #70-588., 1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Insubordination
- National Lead Co., Macintyre Development vs. Local 23175, Iron Ore Miners DAL, 11/2/70. #70-589, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Switching Shifts, Past Practice
- Allied Chemical Corp. vs. Local 8-618, OCAWIU, 9/70. #70-590, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Ro-Ames Industries, Inc. vs. Local 1922, IBEW, 11/70. #70-591, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Demand for Bill of Particulars, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- United Federation of Teachers vs. Charles Loiancono, Edward Kochian, Vincent Speranzo, Joseph Pacheco, 12/9/70. #70-592, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Brief (UFT), Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Insubordination, Strikes, Absences
- Airequipt Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. District 15, IAM, 9/9/70. #70-593, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Insubordination
- Parke Davis Co. vs. Local 815, IBT, 11/70. #70-594, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Ashland Chemical Co. vs. Federal Union 22026, 9/25/70. #70-595, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- United Board & Carton Corp. vs. Local 344, IBPSPMW, 9/70. #70-596, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Perth Amboy Dry Dock Co. vs. Local 144, Painters Union, 8/70. #70-597, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Armstrong Cork Co. vs. Local 22619, URW, 3/8/71. #70-598, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Absences, Alcoholism
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 3/12/71. #70-599, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Memorandum, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Compensatory Time Off
- The Celotex Corp. vs. Local 660, IBT, 4/7/71. #70-600, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Timeliness, Overtime, Assignment of Work to those Outside Bargaining Unit
- St. John Associates, Inc. & Dataname, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 10/70. #70-601, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Modification
- Bayview Nursing Home & Convalescent Center, Inc. vs. Local 1115, NHHSCHU, 9/14/70. #70-602., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Contract, Correspondence - Bonuses, Shift Differential, Past Practice, Burden of Proof
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 4/9/71. #70-603, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment of Jobs Outside Classification, Definition
- American Cynamid Co. vs. Local 111, ICWU, 2/19/71. #70-604 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Seniority, Reporting Pay
- Honeywell Farms, Inc. vs. Local 584, IBT, 9/70. #70-605, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Federation of Jewish Philanthropies vs. Local 1707, CSAEU, 3/9/71. #70-606, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Arbitrability, overtime pay
- Board of Education of City of New York vs. Richard A. Bertocci, 6/23/71. #70-607, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Grievant Memorandum, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Discrimination
- Great Costal Express vs. Local 641, Independent Merchandise Drivers, 11/28/70. #70-608, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Submission, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Credibility, Quits
- Inter Royal Corp. vs. Lodge 626, IAM, 11/70. #70-609, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Management Rights, Seniority, Past Practice
- Matlack, Inc. vs. Local 469, IBT, 9/70. #70-610, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Breyer Ice Cream Div. Kraft Co. vs. Local 757, IBT, 11/10/70. #70-611, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Assignment to Work Outside Classification, Past Practice
- Howe Richardson Scale Co. vs. Local 1590, IAM, 11/12/70. #70-612, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Union Statement, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Working Conditions, Loafing, Past Practice
- Avnet Electronics vs. District 65, RWDSU, 10/21/70. #70-613, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Polarized Schiabo Nev Co. vs. Local 734, LIUNA, 10/7/70. #70-614, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Insubordination
- New Era Letter Co. vs. Dist. 65, RWDSU, 9/70. #70-615, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Schuster's Express, Inc. vs. Local 641, IBT, 12/70. #70-616, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Absences, leaving Plant Without Permission, Credibility
- Stamford Motors, Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 11/70. #70-617., 1970 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Profanity
- Queen Farms Dairy Co. vs. Local 584, IBT, 11/23/70. #70-618, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Decision, arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Dishonesty
- RCA Institute, Inc. vs. the Faculty Association, 11/19/70. #70-619 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assigning Bargaining Unit Work to Non-Bargaining Unit Employees
- Scott Brothers vs. Local 641, IBT, 11/70. #70-620, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  Correspondence - Postponed by Parties Due to Unavailability of Grievant
- Schuster's Express Inc. vs. Local 641, IBT, 12/14/70. #70-621, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Fights and Altercation
- Acme Outwear Inc. vs. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 12/70. #70-622, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Leave of Absence, Layoff
- Charles Bruning Co. vs. Local 365, UAW, 11/70. #70-623, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- New York City vs. Municipal Guild of Radio and TV Technicians, 11/70. #70-624, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Durez Plastics vs. Local 2112, IAM, 12/22/70. #70-625, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Absences, Suspension
- Eastern Freightways vs. Local 560, IBT, 11/25/70. #70-626, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties at Hearing
- South Bay Pontiac Motors vs. Local 259, UAW, 12/70. #70-627, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- General Envelope Co., Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 11/23/70. #70-628, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Absences, Tardiness, Improper Personal Conduct
- Plaza Artist Materials, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 12/22/70. #70-629, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Holiday Pay
- New Bedford Rayon, Inc. vs. TWUA, 11/70. #70-630, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  Correspondence - Holiday Pay, Vacation Pay, Fringe Benefits
- Eastern Corrugated Container Corp. vs. Local 381, FBCBDW, 1/71. #70-631, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Falsification of Records, Dishonesty, Past Practice
- City of new York vs. District Council 37, AFSCME, 12/28/70. #70-632, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendation, Impasse Panel's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation.
- S.S. White Co. vs. District 15, IAM, 1/20/70. #70-633, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Memorandum, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Insubordination, Leaving Plant Without Permission
- National Lead Co.-Titanium Div. vs. Local 8-830, OCAWIU, 3/24/71. #70-634, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Post-Hearing Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Credibility, Insurance Fund, Contract Interpretation
- Nestle Co. Inc. vs. PCK Employees Union, Independent, 3/23/71. #70-635, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Brief, Employee Position on Issue, Employer Post-Hearing Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Vacation Pay
- S.B. Thomas Co., Inc. vs. Local 802, Bakery Drivers Union (BDU), 12/28/70. #70-636, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Dishonesty
- Seaford Union Free School Dist. No. 6 vs. Local 100, SEIU, 1/71. #70-637, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment to Work Outside Classification
- Lipe-Rollway Corp. vs. Local 14929, Intl. Union of District 50, 5/6/71. #70-638, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Temporary Layoff
- Toms River Education Association vs. Toms River Board of Education, 2/23/71. #70-639, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Leaves of Absence
- Neapco Products, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, 3/12/71. #70-640, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Post-Hearing Brief, Employee Post-Hearing Brief, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Overtime
- Paramus Board of Education vs. Paramus Education Association, 1/8/71. #70-641, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  Mediator's Notes, Board Proposals, Contract Modifications, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiation
- Lesnow Manufacturing Co. vs. ACWA, 2/24/71. #70-642, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Layoffs, Seniority, Bonuses, Rates of Pay, Piecework
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 7/29/71. #70-643, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Retention Rights
- Bayview Nursing Center vs. Local 1115, NHHEU, 3/71. #70-644, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Vail Ballou Press, Inc. vs. Local 89 Binghamton Bookbinders, 4/17/71. #71-645, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Changes in Work Assignments
- Grove Motor Co., Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 6/14/71. #71-646, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Credibility, Layoff
- Reichhold Chemical Inc. vs. Local 8-190, OCAWIU, 2/19/71. #71-648 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Alcoholism
- Perth Amboy Dry Docks vs. Lodge 638, International Brotherhood of Boilmakers, 3/71. #71-649., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Artcraft Theatre Equipment vs. Local 44, UDU, 2/71. #71-650, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- New York City Dept. of Parks vs. District Council No. 13, AFSCME, 2/71. #71-651, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  Mediator's Notes, Correspondence - Wages
- Webster Lens Co. vs. Local 408, UOWU, 3/25/71. #71-652, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment of Additional Work
- RCA Institutes, Inc. vs. Faculty Association, 12/7/71. #71-653, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Layoff, Holiday Pay, Bargaining History
- New York City Civil Service Commissioner vs. District Council 37, AFSCME, Local 1180, CWA, 3/4/71. #71-654, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  Correspondence - Arbitrator's Appointment as Neutral Member of the Test Validation Board for Promotion to Administrative Assistant
- Allied New York Services, Inc. vs. Local 553, IBT, 4/6/71. #71-655, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Tardiness, Credibility
- Glen Rock Knitting Mills vs. Local 222, ILGWU, n.d. #71-656 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Johnson & Johnson Ethican, Inc. vs. Local 630, TWUA, 3/26/71. #71-657, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer's Opening Statement, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Overtime, Concerted Action
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 6/4/71. #71-658, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Hearing Transcript, Original Draft of Decision, Issue, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employee Reply Brief, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Medical Insurance
- Don-Dee Trucking vs. Local 641, Merchandise Drivers, 2/71. #71-659, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- City of new York vs. Local 1180, CWA, #71-666 (Box 31, Folder 1)